

ABOUT ME

Fullstack Developer with robust problemsolving skills and experience in creating and designing software in a test-driven environment.

I thoroughly enjoy many different fields of technology. Coding daily is my passion, and I continuously refine my skills by working on custom programs for everyday problems or Intranet websites for personal and professional purposes.

As a passionate developer, I am excited about my next position as a Fullstack Web Developer.

MY CONTACT

Phone:

347-410-2593

Email:

joegoolic15@gmail.com

Website:

https://www.josephgoolic.com/

GitHub:

https://github.com/Joegoolic

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/jeg1595

Address:

Staten Island, NY 10306

JOSEPH GOOLIC

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

Targeting an Internship or Entry-Level Opportunity

WORK EXPERIENCE

Inventory Manager/Computer Technician

Icompny

June 2020 to July 2021

- Building computers for customers that fit individual needs
- Offering Technical Support for customers regarding various hardware and software difficulties
- Scaled and reimplemented Inventory Management system to work for the entire warehouse of computers
- Created and enforced rule-set for employees to follow for an inventory management system.
- Implemented system for the recycling of returned computers to be resold as refurbished

Process Guide Manager

Amazon

Sep. 2018 to June 2020

- Managed the team to track the Inventory Statistics replenishing inventory
- Used Proficiency in Windows and The Office suite to educate the team and communicate with Higher managers.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Coding Languages:

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, Python,C++

Frameworks/Systems:

Visual Studio Basic, Git Management, Django, React.js, Express.js, Node.js, AWS ES3, AWS Route 53, AWS LightSail, Django API, AJAX, Linux, Linux CLI, Office Suite

EDUCATIONAL TRAINING

College of Staten Island

Bachelor of Computer Science

- Enrolled since Sept. 2020 to present
- Graduating December 2022.

Kingsborough Community College

Associates Degree in Liberal Arts

• Attended from Sept. 2018 to June 2020